谢谢你们请我们过来吃饭
Thank you guys for having us over.
多有意思  夫妻派对
Yeah, this is fun, couples night.
我不知道为什么我们不多来几次
I don't know why we don't hang out...
这样的夫妻聚会
...with married couples more often.
因为每次我们吃饭
Because every time we do...
你总是开玩笑要夫妻交换
...you make jokes about swinging
把他们吓跑了
and scare them away.
你是指那对葡萄牙人
You mean that Portuguese couple?
就像你没做过蠢事一样
Yeah, like you wouldn't have done it.
嗨  大伙  我有个好消息.
Hey, you guys, I have great news.
罗斯  我们似乎还在吃饭
We're kind of in the middle of dinner.
呃...我已经吃过了  不过...好吧
Oh, well, I already ate, but sure.
猜猜今天工作时发生了什么
Guess what happened at work today.
一只恐龙在一百万年前死了
A dinosaur died a million years ago?
应该是六千五百万年前  请闭嘴
Try 65 million years ago. And then try...
我的终身任职考察会议今天开了
My tenure review board met today,
我听说进展得不错.
and I hear it's looking really good.
你知道这在理论界里
Yeah, do you have any idea
意味着什么吗
what this means in academic circles?
我可以留下来了.
I am gonna get laid.
-嘿  大伙  -嘿
- Hi, you guys. - Hey.
意大利风味
Oh, ltalian.
还有人好说话吗
No one-- No one wanted seconds, right?
不  不  我很好
No, I'm good.
嘿  你们一定不相信
Guys, you're never gonna believe it.
猎头给我打了电话
This headhunter called me.
说古驰要面试我
I have a meeting tomorrow with Gucci.
古驰要聘用我
Gucci wants me.
-我快终身任职了  -祝贺你
- I'm up for tenure. - Congratulations.
你也是  真巧
You too. What are the odds?
猜猜发生了什么
Guess what?
我终于把那个种子从我的牙齿里弄出来了.
I finally got that seed out of my teeth.
我都不知道最应该为谁高兴了
I don't know who I'm happiest for.
我知道  他一整天都在弄它
I do. He's been working on that all day.
《老友记》  第十季  第14集  "康斯薇拉公主"驾到
Friends S10E14 The One With Princess Consuela
嘿  莫妮卡
Hey, Mon, was it weird
把你的姓改成盖勒·宾奇怪吗
changing your name to Geller Bing?
不  不  让人们知道也挺好的
No. No, it felt nice to acknowledge this.
-你是在哪办的   -呃...
- Where'd you go to do it? - The--
姓名部门
The Ministry of Names...
...局
...Bureau.
你没有改过
You never did it.
我很抱歉  变成正式的宾家人
I'm sorry. It's just the idea of--
让人想想就...
Of being an official Bing.
嘿   我得让你知道...
Hey, I will have you know that--
我真是在开玩笑  就让孩子姓盖勒算了
Who am I kidding? Let's call the kid Geller
让宾随着我到死
and let Bing die with me.
-给你  -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thanks.
亲爱的  你想要我随你的姓吗
Honey, would you want me to take your name?
随便你吧
Oh, it's up to you.
这是你的名字
It's your name.
是要跟随你一辈子的
You've gotta live with it.
试试吧  叫我汉尼根夫人
Let's see. Call me Mrs. Hannigan.
汉尼根夫人
Mrs. Hannigan?
什么 没见我忙着呢吗
What? Can't you see I'm in the middle of something?
我喜欢
I like it.
-嘿  大伙  -嘿  乔伊
- Hey, guys. - Hey, Joe.
还有一些东西
We've got a couple of things
我们要去新房子那检查
we've got to check out at the new house.
你想和我们一起去吗
You want to come?
不  谢了
No, thank you.
我们搬家你不高兴了
You're not happy about us moving...
但你是唯一没有看过我们新房子的人.
...but you're the only one who hasn't seen the house.
是啊  和我们一起去吧
Yeah, come with us.
你会知道那离这里很近
You'll see how close it is.
不  才不近
No, it's not close.
你说它在"艾斯克柔"
You said it was in escrow.
我在地图上都找不到这地方
I couldn't even find that on the map.
乔伊  求你来吧
Joey, please come.
你对我们真的很重要
It would mean so much to us.
知道吗
You know what?
你们是我的朋友
You are my friends.
我要支持你们
I want to be supportive.
我会和你们一起去的  我要副驾驶座
I will come with you. Shotgun.
讨厌
Damn it.
一会见
See you guys later.
我们在十一点接你
We'll pick you up at 11.
真高兴你能来
So glad you're coming.
好
All right.
真不错
Good for you.
你成熟了
That was really mature.
什么 不  我去那所白痴房子
What? No, the only reason I'm going...
唯一原因是
...to their stupid house is
要去说出里面所有的缺点
to point out everything wrong with it...
好让他们不搬家
...so they don't move.
我要他们留在这里
I'm gonna make them stay here.
你这是种奇怪的成长
You're a strange kind of grownup.
乔伊  你不能让别人
Joey, you can't make someone do something
做他们不愿做的事
they don't want to do.
相信我
Believe me.
有些事我想让
There's something I've been trying to
迈克在床上做  但他...
get Mike to do in bed, and--
我们现在能不谈那个吗
Can we not talk about that now?
好吧  假正经
All right. Prude.
听着  莫妮卡和钱德勒
Look, Monica and Chandler
真的很喜欢那所房子
really love this house.
你不应该说服他们住在这里
You are not gonna talk them into staying here.
嘿  我能说服人们做任何事情
Hey, I can convince people to do anything, you know?
我打赌我能让迈克做那事
I bet I could even get Mike to do that thing.
到底什么事儿
What is it?
我才不要帮你做那个
I am not gonna help you do that!
哦  我的天
Oh, my God.
嗨  我来见古驰的坎贝尔先生
Hi. I'm here to see Mr. Campbell, with Gucci.
位子也许就是古驰公司预定的
The reservation's probably under Gucci.
听着像"嘉琪"
It's spelled like "Gukki"
也许会弄错
which can be confusing.
坎贝尔现在还没到
Mr.Campbell's not here yet.
让我把你带到他的位子
Let me show you to his table.
哦   我的天  那是我的老板.
Oh, my God. That's my boss.
你必须把位子安排在别处
You have to seat us somewhere else.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry,
这一直是坎贝尔先生的桌子
that's always Mr.Campbell's table.
但我的老板不能在这看到我
But my boss cannot see me.
我在面试另一个工作
I'm interviewing for another job.
我知道  面试"嘉琪"吗
I know. With "Gukki."
-瑞秋  -我在约会
- Rachel? - I'm on a date.
太棒了
That's great.
是啊
Yeah, it is.
你知道  太难了
Yeah, you know, it's tough.
单身母亲  还要事业
Single mom. Career.
但还是要寻找幸福
You gotta get out there.
你很有精力
Well, you've got a good energy.
-瑞秋  -是的  嗨
- Rachel? - Yes, hi.
-詹姆斯·坎贝尔  -嗨
- James Campbell. - Hi.
-抱歉  -请坐
- Excuse us. - Please.
他很可爱.
He's cute.
那么...
So...
你的简历让人印象深刻
...your resume is quite impressive.
我的简历...
My resume?
我不会把我的
I wouldn't-- I wouldn't call
线上约会资料叫做简历
my online dating profile a resume.
约会材料
Dating profile?
不  我是说...我是说工作简历
No, I'm-- I'm talking about the work resume.
现在怎么没人
Whatever happened to
想唱就唱了呢
just singing for no reason?
或许是因为别人会觉得奇怪
Maybe people found it weird.
那么...
So....
你为什么想离开拉夫·劳伦
Why do you want to leave Ralph Lauren?
什么
What?
-我  我没有  -你没有
- I...I don't. - You don't?
不  我喜欢那里
No, I love-- I love it there.
如果你不想离开
Well, if you don't want to leave,
为什么我们在这里吃午饭呢
why are we having this lunch?
什么
What?
那是雨果·博斯
That's Hugo Boss?
这个地方太令人压抑了
This place is so depressing.
如果我在这里工作
If I had to work here,
我会自杀的
I'd kill myself.
显然你还没
But you obviously haven't.
有什么需要帮忙的
How can I help you?
我想要改我的名字
I need to change my name, please.
我想改掉它因为我在逃避法律
See, I need to change it because I'm hiding from the law.
你很有趣
You're fun.
请填一下这个表格
You need to fill out this form.
好  我想了解下
Okay. Well, just so I know--
我只是不知道应该怎么做  我姓布菲
I don't know how it works. My name is Buffay...
我丈夫叫汉尼根
...and my husband's name is Hannigan.
那么应该是"布菲·汉尼根"
So is it supposed to be "Buffay-Hannigan"
还是"汉尼根·布菲"
or "Hannigan-Buffay"?
你想怎样就怎样
It can be anything you want.
也不是我想叫什么就叫什么吧
Well, not anything.
是的  你想叫啥叫啥
Yeah. Anything.
哦  那需要花些时间
Oh, this could take a while.
-站到一边去  -好
- Get out of my line. - Okay.
-嘿  -嘿  菲比
- Hey. - Hey, Pheebs.
不再是了  我今天改了名字
Oh, not anymore. I changed it today.
抱歉  汉尼根夫人
Oh, I'm sorry, Mrs. Hannigan.
又错了
Wrong again.
显然你能改成任何你想要的名字
Apparently, you can change it to anything.
所以我想"好吧
So I thought, "All right,
这是发挥想象力的好机会"
here's an opportunity to be creative."
所以来见过康斯薇拉·巴娜娜·哈莫克公主
So meet Princess Consuela Banana Hammock.
那是我想给我们宝宝的名字
That's what we were gonna name the baby.
-菲比  -康斯薇拉公主
- Phoebe. - Princess Consuela.
你真的把你的名字改成那个了
You seriously changed your name to that?
好吧  从今往后
Okay, so from now on,
我们得叫你康斯薇拉公主了
we have to call you Princess Consuela?
不  我会让我的朋友叫我瓦莱丽
No, I'm gonna have my friends call me Valerie.
-嘿  面试如何  -不妙
- Hey, how did the interview go? - Not good.
你知道吗  面试后我经常也这么觉得
You know. I always feel that way after an interview.
我打赌结果会比你想得好
I'll bet it went better than you think.
我没有得到古驰的工作
Well, I didn't get the job at Gucci
还丢了拉夫·劳伦的工作
and I got fired from Ralph Lauren.
这面试的确不好
That is a bad interview.
你在说什么呀
What are you talking about?
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
我老板在同一家餐厅
My boss was at the same restaurant
我在那里面试
where I was having my interview...
他听见了一切
...and he heard everything.
后来他把我叫到他的办公室
Later, he calls me into his office
告诉我他要解雇我
and tells me he'll have to let me go...
因为我没有团队精神
...because I'm not a team player.
然后我说"等等  我有"
And I said, "Wait a minute. Yes, I am."
然后我得在那里坐45分钟
And then I had to sit there for 45 minutes...
而他证明了  事实他说的那样
...while he proved that that, in fact, was true.
哦  真抱歉
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
嘿
Hey.
这...这是什么
What--? What's this?
是一瓶香槟
Why, it's a bottle of champagne.
它为什么在这
Why is this here?
-罗斯  -我想是
- Ross. - I guess it's here...
因为我得到了终身职位
...because I got tenure!
-恭喜你  -恭喜你
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
这是我职业生涯中最伟大的一天
This is the single greatest day of my professional career.
-甘瑟  六个杯子  -六个
- Gunther. Six glasses. - Six?
你要我也喝
You want me to join you?
我以为乔伊也在这儿
I thought Joey was here.
五个好了
Five is good.
明天我的咖啡里要有大鼻涕了
Wow, I'm gonna have a loogey in my coffee tomorrow.
以色列香槟
Israeli champagne.
还是香草味的呢
And it's vanilla.
我得了终身职位  又不是中了彩票
I got tenure. I didn't win the lottery.
嘿  瑞秋  你的事怎么了
Hey, Rach, so how did your thing go?
挺好
Good.
但是要几天以后再出结果.
But I'm not going to hear about that for a couple days.
你知道吗  你会得到工作的
Oh, you know what, you're gonna get it.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
你能吗
Can you?
好的  敬罗斯
All right, everybody, here's to Ross.
为了多年的艰苦工作终于有了回报
And to years of hard work finally paying off.
也为了懂得你的工作
And to knowing that your career
并不意味着所有事情
doesn't mean everything.
但也意味着很多
But also knowing it means a lot.
更为了多彩丰富的生活
But more importantly, to full, well-rounded lives.
以工作为中心
That center around work.
-敬罗斯  -敬罗斯
- To Ross. - To Ross.
你知道最棒的是什么吗
You know what the best part about this is?
我永远都不会失业
I can never be fired.
-哦  天啊  -不  说真的
- Oh, God. - No, seriously.
我有了终生工作保障
I have job security for life.
我是说我永远都不会为它而担心
You know? I mean, I never have to worry.
看看你  看你多为我高兴
Oh, look at you. Look how happy you are for me.
不  不是那样  我今天被辞退了
No, it's not that. I got fired today.
而且又没有得到新的工作
And I didn't get the other job.
瑞秋  很抱歉
Rach, I'm so sorry.
太好了  我觉得自己像个白痴
Great, I feel like an idiot.
不  没什么  你不知道
No, it's okay. You didn't know.
你们就不知道提醒下
Little heads-up would've been nice.
谢谢你能让我们再看房子
Thank you for letting us see the house again.
也谢谢你给我们解释"契约"的意思
And thank you for explaining to us what escrow means.
我已经忘了你说了什么
I've already forgotten what you said,
但是  谢谢你
but thank you.
想待多久就待多久
Take as long as you want.
你们看完之后告诉我就好
Just let me know when you're through.
很高兴你能来
So glad you decided to come.
我也是  这地方真好
Me too. Yeah, this place is great.
真为你们高兴
So happy for you guys.
但是  我希望你们喜欢菌类
Although, you know, I hope you like fungus.
-什么  -菌类
- What? - Fungus.
它们在任何地方都有
Yeah. Place is full of it.
不  才不是
No, it's not.
我们叫人来检测过房子
We had an inspection
他们什么都没找到
and they didn't find anything.
好吧  我想我毫无原因的
Okay. Then I guess I have dry eyes
眼睛干燥喉咙痛
and a scratchy throat for no reason.
或许是因为
Maybe it's because you hung your head
来的一路上
out the window like a dog...
你都像狗一样把头伸到窗外
...the whole ride here.
也许是
Maybe.
那这就是客厅
So this is the living room, huh?
真暗啊
It's pretty dark.
才不是
No, it's not.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我刚才好像在角落看到只蝙蝠
I think I just saw a bat in the corner.
当你的头伸在车窗外的时候
When your head was hanging out the window,
没有撞到信箱吧
it didn't hit a mailbox, did it?
也许
Maybe.
我只是觉得你们
Look, I just think you guys can do
可以有更好的选择
better than this house, you know?
或者可以买到更好的房子
Or any other house for that matter.
哦  乔伊
Oh, Joey.
我们知道你觉得不好受  但我们...
We know you're having a hard time with this, but we--
真的喜欢这里
We love it here.
好吧  好吧  如果你喜欢这所房子
Fine! Ok. If you love this house so much...
你们就住这里吧
...you should live here. Okay?
我只是希望你们能习惯那种奇怪的声音
I hope you get used to that weird humming sound.
-乔伊  我们知道那是你  -不...
- Joey, we know that's you. - No...
不是的
...it's not.
-欢迎回来  -我想你了
- Welcome back. - I missed you.
-哦  我也是  -有什么新鲜事
- Oh, me too. - So, what's new?
我不再叫菲比·布菲了
Well, I am no longer Phoebe Buffay.
太棒了  你改名字了
That's great. You changed your name?
是的
Yes, I did.
见过康斯薇拉·巴娜娜·哈莫克公主
Meet Princess Consuela Banana Hammock.
-你在开玩笑  -不
- You're kidding, right? - Nope.
-你真的那么做了  -对
- You really did that? - Yep.
你不能那么做
You can't do that.
为什么
Why?
为什么  那很好玩
Why? It's fun.
很不同  没有人有那样的名字
It's different. No one else has a name like it.
好吧  我也去改我的名字
Then I'm gonna change my name.
好  你要改成什么
Great. Okay, what are you gonna change it to?
大便·袋
Crap Bag.
迈克·大便·袋
Mike Crap Bag?
不  没有迈克  只是大便·袋
No. No "Mike." No, just "Crap Bag."
名大便  姓袋
First name: Crap. Last name: Bag.
你不是认真  对吧
You're not serious, right?
我是认真的
Yeah, I'm serious.
很好玩  很不同
It's fun, it's different,
没有人用这样的名字
and no one else has a name like that.
那好极了
Well, then great.
如果你喜欢  我就喜欢
If you love it, I love it.
我的确喜欢  我也喜欢你的名字
I do love it. And I love your name.
我喜欢康斯薇拉公主
I love Princess Consuela.
我喜欢大便
And I love Crap.
-你是谁   -哦  嗨  我是乔伊
- Who are you? - Oh, hi. I'm Joey.
我的白痴朋友要买这所房子
My stupid friends are buying this house.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是麦肯齐
I'm Mackenzie.
我的白痴父母要卖这所房子
My stupid parents are selling this house.
我恨我的父母
I hate my parents.
我恨我的朋友
I hate my friends.
瞧  我们肯定能做一些事
Look, there's gotta be a way
不让他们交易成功
that we can stop this from happening.
比如
Like what?
你跟我来告诉他们这房子闹鬼
Okay, you come with me and you tell them that the house is haunted.
这么幼稚  八岁啊你
What are you, 8?
好吧  你有什么好主意
Okay. Let's hear your great idea.
我没有好主意
I don't have any great ideas.
我八岁
I am 8.
一定要想一个办法  我是说...
There's gotta be a way. I mean, you know...
莫妮卡和钱德勒搬走了
...if Monica and Chandler move here,
菲比和迈克结婚了
and Phoebe's married to Mike...
只剩我和罗斯还有瑞秋
...that just leaves me and Ross and Rach.
你知道意味着什么吗
You know what I mean?
不太知道
I really don't.
我到底怎么办
What am I gonna do?
我觉得我要失去我的朋友了
I feel like I'm losing my friends.
我父母说我能交到新的朋友
My parents say I'll make new friends.
当然  对你而言很容易
Yeah, sure, easy for you.
你这么小  我生活都定型了
You're young. Me? I'm set in my ways.
这就是我妈妈一直说的
This is what my mom was talking about.
抱怨不休的人都是些失败者
Whiners are wieners.
你希望你的朋友开心  对吧
Look, you want your friends to be happy, right?
是的  我想是的
Yeah. Yeah, I guess. Yeah.
那么  如果搬到这里来会让他们开心
Well, if moving here is gonna make them happy,
你难道不希望他们这样做吗
don't you want them to do it?
希望啊  或许吧
Yeah. Maybe.
那你就应该放手
Then you've gotta let them go.
我恨承认这个  但你...
Oh, I hate to admit it, but you're--
也许是对的
You're probably right.
你怎么这么聪明
How'd you get to be so smart?
我读了很多书.
I read a lot.
还以为我们能成为朋友
Just when I thought we could be friends.
嗨  瑞秋  我刚听说  很抱歉
Oh, hey, Rach. I just heard. I'm so sorry.
哦  谢谢你...
Oh, thank you....
还是不知道我的名字  对吗
You still don't know my name, do you?
现在我不用知道了
Well, now I don't have to.
罗斯  你怎么那么慢
Ross, what is taking you so long?
抱歉  他们建造这门的时候
I'm sorry. It's almost as if
怎么不考虑让你搬家能快些呢
this wasn't built for a quick getaway.
瑞秋
Rachel?
马克   我的天啊
Mark? Oh, my God.
你怎么样
How have you been?
太好了  你记得罗斯
Fantastic. You remember Ross.
当然
Sure.
搬椅子干嘛
What's with the chair?
你知道  在地铁上
You know, you can't always
没有座位...
get a seat on the subway, so....
真聪明
Clever.
你最近怎么样
So how are you?
真不巧  今天出点事儿
You're not catching me on my best day.
整箱的办公用品  不像是要升职啊
Yeah, a box full of your desk stuff doesn't say "big promotion."
不  但也还好
No, but it's good.
你知道...我要休息一段时间...
You know, I'm gonna take some time off...
-做一些慈善工作  -你肯定吗
- ...and do charity work. - Are you sure?
LV现在可能需要人
We may have something at Louis Vuitton.
去它的慈善工作  你有什么消息
Screw charity work. What do you got?
我们边吃饭边讨论吧
Why don't we have dinner and talk?
-我给你打电话  -好吧
- Great. I'll call you. - Okay.
很高兴又见到你
Nice to see you again.
啊...我有终身职位了
Yeah. Yeah. I got tenure.
哦  我的天.
Oh, my God.
看到没有  我告诉你好事会来的
See? I told you something good would come along.
他看起来真不错
And he seemed really nice.
我以前见过他吗
I've met him before?
罗斯  那是马克
Ross, that's Mark.
布明岱尔百货的啊
From Bloomingdale's?
当时你嫉妒得发狂
You were insanely jealous of him.
-那是马克  -是啊
- That is Mark? - Yes.
我恨他
I hate that guy.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
你不能和他吃饭
You cannot go to dinner with him.
什么  你不希望我有这份工作
What? You don't want me to get a job?
当然  我肯定他会给你一份工作
Yeah, I'm sure he'll give you a job.
也许让你当他的"性秘书"
Maybe make you his "sex-cretary."
我是认真的  我只是不相信他
I'm serious. I just don't trust that guy, okay?
罗斯  你知道吗
Ross. You know what--?
好  我们以后再谈  保安来了
Okay, let's talk about it later. There comes security.
我喜欢这个街道
Oh, I love this street.
那么多树  大大的前院  真正的尖桩篱栅
The trees and the big front yards and the actual picket fences.
那是两只狗干上了
Man, those two dogs are going at it.
嘿  你到哪里去了
Hey. Where you been?
哦  只是随处走走
Oh, just, you know, looking around.
你知道吗
But you know what?
这房子太棒了
This house is great.
真的  什么使你改变了
Really? What changed your mind?
那个住在这里的小姑娘让我感觉好很多
The little girl who lives here made me feel better about the whole thing.
乔伊  以前有小姑娘住在这儿
Joey? There was a little girl who lived here,
但三十年前就死了
but she died, like, 30 years ago.
什么
What?
我只是在吓你
I'm just messing with you.
这不好笑
That's not funny.
你知道我害怕小女鬼
You know I'm afraid of little-girl ghosts.
现在你喜欢这房子了
Now that you're okay with the house,
你想看看你的房间吗
do you want to go see your room?
什么
What?
我会有我自己的房间
I get my own room?
你不会认为我们
You don't think we'd buy a house
买了房子却没有给你房间吧
and not have a Joey room, do you?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我能有个鱼缸吗
Hey, can I have an aquarium?
加个做爱秋千
And a sex swing?
不
No.
为什么不行  我会保持干净的
Why not? I'll keep the tank clean.
你先请  巴娜娜·哈莫克女士
After you, Ms. Bananahammock.
谢谢  袋先生
Thank you, Mr. Bag.
-哦  你好 瑞塔  -你最近好嘛
- Oh, hi, Rita. - How are you?
瑞塔是一个按摩的客户
Good. Oh, Rita's a massage client.
哦
Yeah.
你为什么不介绍我
Why don't you introduce me?
瑞塔  这是我的丈夫
Rita, this is my husband.
为什么不告诉她我的名字
Why don't you tell her my name?
好的  我会的  这是我的丈夫大便·袋
Okay, I will. This is-- This is my husband, Crap Bag.
大便·袋
Crap Bag?
如果你需要记得容易点
If you need an easy way to remember it,
就把它想象成一袋子大便
just think of a bag of crap.
-好的  少陪了  -好
- Okay. Excuse me. - Yeah.
好吧  我知道你的意思了
Okay, fine, you made your point.
你能再做我的迈克·汉尼根
Can you please just be Mike Hannigan again?
只要你还是菲比·布菲
Only if you'll be Phoebe Buffay.
布菲·汉尼根怎么样
How about--? How about Buffay-Hannigan?
真的
Really?
是
Yeah.
我是菲比·布菲·汉尼根·巴娜娜·哈莫克
I'm Phoebe Buffay-Hannigan-Banana Hammock.
你知道巴娜娜·哈莫克是什么吗
Do you even know what a banana hammock is?
就是个有趣的字
It's a funny word.
那是一种三角裤
It's a Speedo.
噢  糟了
Oh, crap.
-嘿  瑞秋在吗  -不
- Hey, is Rachel here? - Nope.
她还在吃晚饭
She's still at dinner?
我想是的  她和谁在一起
I guess. Why, who's she with?
是马克
That guy, Mark...
布明岱尔百货那个
...from Bloomingdale's.
她认为他只是对她好
She thinks he's just being nice to her.
但我知道他想和她睡
But I know he really wants to sleep with her.
已经七年了
It's seven years ago.
我的时间机器起作用了
My time machine works.
我们今天在路上碰到他
We ran into him on the street today,
他说也许他有工作给她
and he said he might have a job for her.
但我知道他只是想拉她上床
But I know he just wants to get into her pants.
他想跟她上床又怎样
So, what if he wants to sleep with her?
我是说她单身而且可爱
I mean, she's single, and he's cute.
什么
Excuse me?
哦  拜托
Oh, please.
昨天在地铁上
Yesterday, on the subway, you couldn't stop staring...
你不停地盯着一个大胸脯的女人看
...at that woman with the big breasts the whole time.
告诉你  我那是看她的小孩呢
For your information, I was staring at her baby.
我们就要做父母了
We're about to be parents.
哦  对不起
Oh, sorry.
-嗨  大伙  -嗨
- Hi, you guys. - Hi. So...
晚饭怎么样
...how was dinner?
噢  很棒  马克人很好
Oh, it was great. Mark is so sweet.
哦  是吗  我想知道为什么
Oh, yeah? Yeah, I wonder why?
那个虚情假意的好色者想要什么呢
What could that smarmy letch possibly want?
哦  罗斯  别这样 他已经结婚了
Oh, Ross. Come on. He is happily married.
他的妻子生了双胞胎
His wife just had twins.
我们应该送点什么礼物吗
Should we send something?
工作怎么样
How did the job stuff go?
他给了我一个工作机会
He offered me one.
-太棒了  -恭喜你
- That's great. - Congratulations.
我知道  那很棒
I know, it's amazing.
那很棒  那比我在
It's amazing. It's so much better
拉夫·劳伦要好得多
than what I had at Ralph Lauren.
-薪水很不错  -我们...
- The money is great. - Can we--?
我们能停一停吗
Can we just stop for a second?
是谁说一切都会好起来的
Who said something better would come along?
你不相信我
You didn't believe me.
我告诉你一切都会有起色
I told you everything was gonna work out.
你知道吗
You know what?
这时候该来一瓶以色列佳酿
This calls for a bottle of lsrael's finest.
工作地点在巴黎
The job is in Paris.
我是说  这肥皂剧是很好的机会
I mean, this soap opera is a great gig...
但这样做我是不是就错过机会了
...but am I missing opportunities?
你知道  我总是觉得我自己是个正经的演员
You know, I've always thought of myself as a serious actor.
我是不是应该尝试更多的电影
Should I be trying to do more independent movies?
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道吗
But you know what?
我让我的熊听电话
I'm gonna put you on with my bear.
等等
Hold on.
嘿 小熊  我需要一些事业上的意见
Hey, Bailey, I need some career advice.